One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
Let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
Donut Race!!
All right! While everyone's
busy with their boats, I'll explain how the race works!
The course will be one lap
around Long Ring Long Land!
It might sound easy, but it's anything but!
A team is immediately out of
the race should their boat sink!
In addition, all weapons are allowed
even guns, cannons, explosives,
cutlasses, or anything else!
Whoever complains about unfairness
will be shamed as a pirate!
Porche-chan!
I hope you sink nose dude!
Me?!
We have to win now!
Sinking opponents is fair game.
I'm getting excited!
Do we even have a chance?
Listen up Usopp! Anything happens
to the ladies and I'll filet you!
We will win!
Oh my. Listen to that crazy talk.
Let 'em talk Porche-chan.
We'll sink 'em in three minutes!
Right Monda?!
Fool! No one's ever beat us
in an orthodox-rules game!
Think this race will last
five minutes Hamburg?
Nope.
Now take these Eternal Poses
so that you don't get lost!
Lost?
Leave the island? Why would we do that?
We're taking the shortest route along the inside track!
I don't think it'll be that simple...
Okay! On your marks!
Ready!
Why won't it be so simple?!
Just trust me!
Leave the shore as soon as we start!
Why?!
You're mine.
Donut!
I've got a bad feeling about this!
Tell us why!
Push it! Push it! Push it!
We're gonna teach ya what
this boat exists for!
Oh no! We're too late!
What are these?
Are these traps?
N-Nami! Don't...!
And there they are! The Mothership
Coaster's infamous Barrel Mines!
See you later!
Don't sink right away though!
Give us some fun!
Capote! Give 'em a taste
of your Fishman Karate!
Right!
Sea Surface Splitter!
The boat's come apart!
Our balance...!
Take this!
Special Attack: Flame Star!
That won't work!
Ocho Fleurs!
Eight Flowers
What the...?!
Capote!
Flip!
Oh no!
Yes! Now's our chance!
Usopp swim and pull the boat!
Don't be crazy!
Capote! Monda! Pull yourselves together!
Paddle! Paddle!
Let's get to it, Hamburg.
Really? It's finally time, Boss?
All right! Currently in the lead
is the adorable Cutie Wagon!
In second is the Barrel Tiger.
Oh, yeah! Usopp! Use a dial!
O-Oh right!
All right! I'll use this Breath Dial to...!
Paddling would be faster than this!
Don't you have a Jet Dial?!
Those are impossible to get!
One of our crew members is on the line here!
Yeah! That's the issue!
If we end up losing, they'll definitely take me first!
I can't let that happen! I'm too cute!
You wish. Now just paddle.
What?! This is no time for reading, Robin!
I'm paddling too.
Your hands are, but you don't seem like you're...
Yeah, Robin...
You'll end up like me if
you don't work hard...
I am working hard.
You're more tactful than I thought.
Shall we head straight for the goal,
or shall we sink them instead?
I enjoy the occasional leisurely trip across the goal line.
But I wanna make that chick pay!
Winning isn't enough for me now!
What?!
How is this?
Wonderful, Robin!
Cheater!
Let go!
They already caught on. Too bad.
Capote!
How dare they?!
Let's just keep moving!
We can't let 'em get a bigger lead!
I guess I'll sink them after all.
Oh!
Ahh!
Up ahead are the biggest obstacles
of the course: the Long Coral Reef
and the Long Ring Whirlpool
of Long Cape beyond it!
How will they overcome these?! And...
Oh! Is that...?!
What?
There's someone on the island!
It's "Full Dash" Hamburg!
Atop him, making an appearance at last...
is the Master of Obstruction!
The great scoundrel who
hates fairness; our boss!
"Silver Fox" Foxy!
Him!
I just got an evil idea!
The race is really heating up!
The Long Coral Reef blocks
the course directly ahead!
In the lead is Porche-chan's Cutie Wagon!
Look! It's causing strange-acting currents!
We can't just plunge in recklessly...
Yuck! I can't believe the
race has lasted this long...
Monda! We're counting on you!
But let's not forget there's someone
on land just hoping to interfere:
our boss, "Silver Fox" Foxy!
Just what does he have in store?!
Some inari sushi and
kitsune udon! No charge!
For real?! Thanks! Yum!
We'd love to have a cook like you join us!
Your twirly eyebrow's so cute!
Oh! Maybe I should be Davy Backed right now!
Hey! Some more drinks over here!
Have all you want!
Thanks guys!
Get 'em, Boss!
Yahoo! Just a matter o' time now!
Oh what's this?!
C'mon Nami! Paddle!
Not yet!
But they're getting ahead!
I said not yet!
The Cutie Wagon uses this
chance to continue forward and plunge into the Long Coral Reef!
Let's go, Monda!
Wait! Oh my! What's happening?!
Monda!
Oh... They came back.
Oh my! The Cutie Wagon
has been sent backwards!
What in the world happened?!
No! Why?!
See? I knew something
was up with these currents.
Okay! Let's increase speed!
R-Right!
Try again Monda!
This way!
Whoa! What the...?!
Ahh! There it is at last!
Devilish interference from you-know-who!
A smoke screen...!
Oh my!
Operation White Out is a great success!
Let's see you find your way
through this coral maze blind!
Success?
How in the...?!
They got through! With no
trouble at all! How did they do it?!
Just as I thought!
Meanwhile the Cutie Wagon...
Oh no!
...has been sent back again!
What's going on?!
The boat's moving on its own!
This is a maze of sea currents.
Of sea currents?
Yep. The whirlpool up ahead is
causing strange currents in this reef,
full of smaller whirlpools.
So we don't need to see ahead!
The currents will carry us through...
as long as we take the right entrance!
Awesome! That's the power of our navigator!
Hurray!
Curses!
But their joy is short-lived!
Beyond the coral forest is the Long Ring!
Usopp! Quit freaking out and fire it!
Fire what?!
An Impact!
I-I told you we don't have it! Nope!
Oh? Then what's this?
When did you...?!
Hurry! Before the whirlpool sucks us in!
It's okay! I don't mind!
'Cause it's my shoulder!
No wonder you seemed so calm!
You had this in mind from the start...
Fine!
Oh! The Barrel Tiger...
No, more than that! They're flying!
The Barrel Tiger takes a miraculously big lead!
Does this spell defeat for
the indomitable Cutie Wagon?!
We underestimated them a bit!
We're counting on you!
Combine!
Two Fish Engine!
No! They haven't lost yet!
Their fishman muscle and shark fin
combo doubles their engine speed!
They zip through the coral and
turbulent waves to close the gap!
The race is half over!
Meanwhile the Barrel Tiger
paddles desperately!
Get up Usopp!
Where am I?
Just start paddling!
Your arm is twisted in an odd direction.
What's that?
It's a course marker.
It says to go right.
Okay! Right we go!
Like we'd fall for that!
Oh my! Our boss's Ploy #18,
"Operation Lie to Them" has failed!
Truly formidable! Does this girl
not believe anything?!
Shut up you!
She's foul-mouthed too!
The race continues!
Barrel Tiger is still in the lead!
What are these columns of water?!
They also clear the long waves
that reach high into the sky!
Natural phenomenon?!
Granny...
Bos-, no, Granny...
Yeah... I think I'm done for...
Our boss unleashes a third nasty trick!
Oh! You on the boat! Please save me!
Unbelievable! She completely
ignores a helpless, sick grandmother!
Is she heartless, or does she
only care about herself?!
Whatever the case,
Navigator Nami has a heart of ice!
Will you shut up already?!
I'd never fall for that crap!
She's foul-mouthed too!
Look! It's the goal!
The finish is close at hand!
Not so fast!
The Cutie Wagon has caught up!
Who will be the winner of
Round #1's Donut Race?!
Who will be the winner?!
I told you...
Cut it out! You're annoying!
She even sees through "Operation Fake Goal"!
Formidable! Truly formidable!
I have a question for her now!
What does it mean to "believe"?
I don't care!
Oh it's too late! Her heart's
already closed! She's a heathen!
The real goal is near though.
No more Impacts!
Yeah I know!
Meanwhile Porche-chan's team has
tragically stopped at the fake goal!
What happened to the race?
Hey! Where is everyone?!
The purity of your heart is dazzling!
But you've been duped!
Pay attention Porche-chan!
So many idiots!
I'll be too embarrassed to live
if we lose to these guys!
They'll take our crew too! That's even worse!
Oh no! This goal is a fake!
What?! Who would be so evil?!
Eep!
The Barrel Tiger is finally
approaching Long Bamboo Cape!
The goal is just beyond it!
This is the homestretch!
He's right! There's the goal!
Wait!
But they're catching up to us!
We're no match for their speed!
That's it Usopp! Can you
knock that bamboo down?!
The bamboo?!
All right!
Like that?!
Do more!
Full speed Capote! Monda!
We have to sink them!
Wow! Bingo!
Oh no! Capote!
They'll pay for this!
Cutie Baton!
What's that? Flower magic?
Flower Shurikens!
Ah they're throwing stars... Yikes!
Oh no! We've sprung a leak!
It's okay! We can make it!
The goal is right there!
Let's make a run for it!
Round #1 of the Davy Back Fight;
the Donut Race...
Is about to reach a conclusion!
Stay strong Monda! We
can't let them beat us!
We'll lose if we don't do something!
Stay in line with them!
Right Boss!
Nami-san! Robin-chan!
You speedy ladies are lovely!
Man you guys almost won...
Huh? We are winning!
For now! But look!
Our boss is there!
So?! What can he do now?!
Our boss is just like you.
He has Devil Fruit powers.
Slow Beam!
And the winner is the Cutie Wagon!
Our idol Porche-chan has won the first round of the Davy Back Fight!
All right! Way to go!
Oh! Thanks everyone!
You're the greatest Porche-chan!
It's only natural I won!
Now let's swipe us a crew member!
No one's a match for the Foxy Pirates!
Wha...?
All right! Time for you to
hand over a crew member!
Are you guys hurt?! Are you okay?!
Yes we're all right.
What happened?
Beats us...
That's what we'd like to know!
Did we end up losing?
You were about to win, but then you suddenly got slow and they passed you
There's no need to be mystified!
It was caused by Slowmo Photons!
Hey! What did you do to Nami's team?!
Slowmo Photons...?
They're a type of particle
unlike anything currently known.
Whatever this light touches--
whether it's alive, liquid, or even gas--
it physically loses a fixed amount of speed
while retaining all other energy.
I don't get it! Are you stupid or something?!
He snapped at me...
Oh no! Boss!
But that sounds too ridiculous...
...to be real?
You surely know that such childish claims have no merit in these waters!
Everything they touch slows down!
That's the power of Slowmo Photons!
Oh now that makes sense!
After eating the Slow Slow Fruit
I became a "slow person"
capable of producing these
particles from my body!
Observe its power!
Yikes! He slowed a flying cannonball!
Slow Beam!
The effect lasts approximately thirty seconds.
It'll regain its original speed afterward,
as if nothing had happened.
Can't believe your eyes? This is--!
Boss!
Crap! So that's what happened to us?!
So this is the reason they're
strangely confident about the game.
What a joke of a power...
Do you get it now?! You lost!
Victory in Round #1's Donut Race...
goes to us!
Oh my! You were so close too!
That concludes Round #1!
Now for the long-awaited spoils of war!
It's time to call one member
of the opposing crew!
The first person I want is...
you!
The ship doctor! Tony Tony Chopper!
Me?!
Bring him here at once!
Oh no! Chopper!
What a rare creature!
You're way softer than I imagined!
Oh Boss! Let me touch him too!
Nauseatingly cute!
He's ours now!
Chopper!
So that creep was after Chopper?
Well I guess he is the
rarest of rare animals...
He's into cute things?
Or furs perhaps?
This is no time to chat!
This is serious!
They just took our friend!
Guys...
All right Dr. Chopper.
You're a member of my crew now.
You need to pledge loyalty to me!
Now, put on this mask...
Guys...!
I'm sorry we lost Chopper...!
Damn!
This is a true rarity!
A talking reindeer! Amazing!
Let's be buddies!
Yo! Comrade!
Guys!
I only set sail so I could be with you guys!
No! I-I don't want this!
Luffy! I only set sail
because you invited me to!
I don't wanna go with these guys...!
No! I'm the Straw Hat Pirates'
ship doctor, Tony Tony Chopper!
I don't want this!
Quit your griping, Chopper!
You're being a poor sport!
Zoro...
You're the one who decided to set sail!
No one else is to blame if
you end up dying somewhere!
Only you are!
We agreed to this game.
Usopp and everyone else did their best!
No one in the pirate world would
sympathize with your tears!
A real man...
...would roll up his sleeves and
watch the rest of the contest quietly!
How can you say that?!
Don't you know how he feels?!
All right! Do anything you like with me!
Chopper...
All right!
Whoa!
That swordsman is awesome!
All right! Teach 'em a lesson, Zoro!
Get Chopper back!
Let's take him next, Boss!
This reindeer's got guts!
Let's get the second round started.
So moving! I'm moved to tears!
Yeah. There's still two rounds left.
We're gonna take back our precious
emergency food... and then some.
Sanji! We're counting on you!
The exchange is finished as the Davy Back Fight suddenly explodes with excitement!
Huh? Wait, Chopper's in the second round.
But they took him.
You're right.
That's the real thrill of this game!
We told you!
You can't change your roster!
No replacements allowed!
In other words, only the other
two Straw Hat contestants...
Can participate in Round #2's Groggy Ring!
Team Foxy already has the advantage!
What?!
You can drop out too, if you want.
No, but you can, loser.
I find it hard to believe
they'll work as a team...
Say what?!
Stop that!
I'll now explain the rules of Groggy Ring!
There's a field and two goals!
Knock the balls into them and you win!
However, the balls are no ordinary balls!
They're people!
Both teams, select someone to be a ball!
Which of you's gonna be the ball?!
Here's your ball mark!
Who made you boss?!
You be the ball, Moss Head!
Oh, there it is! Their entrance song!
It's the undefeated elites of Groggy Ring!
Yes! Defeat is impossible for them!
Crush 'em!
The famous Groggy Monsters
have just taken the field!
At the lead is "Full Dash" Hamburg!
He's followed by "Tackle Machine" Pickles!
Last but not least is Big Pan the wotan;
a half-fishman half-giant!
This is literally a monstrous march!
Now, then!
What is that?!
What is that giant fishman?!
They're putting the ball mark on him!
Let's see you win this!
Seem like a good match?
Yep.